const quiz = {
    topic: "Raccoons Server",
    level: "Easy Peasy",
    perQuestionScore: 1,
    questions:[
    {
        question: "What is the server mascot?",
        choices: ["Bee", "Cat", "Raccoon", "Panda"],
        correctAnswer: "Raccoon",
    },
    {
        question: "Who was the first server member?",
        choices: ["SonicBliss", "AkiraZeZero", "Bees_In_Da_Trap", "Abrillion"],
        correctAnswer: "AkiraZeZero",
    },
    {
        question: "Why a Raccoon?",
        choices: ["We sleep alot", "We are phat", "We live in trash", "We never sleep"],
        correctAnswer: "We never sleep",
    },
    {
        question: "Who dies most in our Minecraft server?",
        choices: ["AkiraZeZero", "Murkderose", "0_Cato_0", "Dara_run"],
        correctAnswer: "0_Cato_0",
    },
    { 
        question: "What does 'TFT' stand for?",
        choices: ["Team Fight Team", "To Fight Together", "Teams Fighting Together", "Team Fight Tactics"],
        correctAnswer: "Team Fight Tactics",
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the most hateful member in the server?",
        choices: ["Playboy_Travo", "Bees_In_Da_Trap", "Abrillion", "SonicBliss"],
        correctAnswer: "Bees_In_Da_Trap",
    },
    {
        question: "What was the first big group game?",
        choices: ["Fall Guys", "Gartic Telephone", "Pokemon Unite", "Minecraft"],
        correctAnswer: "Pokemon Unite",
    },
    {
        question: "Who made the really big moon in our Minecraft server?",
        choices: ["Bees_In_Da_Trap", "Murkderose", "Playboytravo","SonicBliss" ],
        correctAnswer: "Bees_In_Da_Trap",
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the youngest member in our server?",
        choices: ["Josue-lacks-a- lot", "Alexa12344", "Taylor","Ryder DaBoss" ],
        correctAnswer: "Alexa12344",
    },
    {
        question: "What member in our server is the 'Meme-a-saurus'",
        choices: ["Abrillion", "Dara_run", "Alantheonly", "Twistedcrater"],
        correctAnswer: "Abrillion",
    },
    {
        question: "How old is Sonic the Hedgehog?",
        choices: ["12", "18", "16", "15"],
        correctAnswer: "15",
    },
    {
        question: "What pokemon is considered 'Murkderose's' pokemon when playing pokemon unite?",
        choices: ["Lapras", "Goodra", "Slowbro", "Dragonite"],
        correctAnswer: "Goodra",
    },
    {
        question: "Who NEVER rage quits?",
        choices: ["AkiraZeZero", "0_Cato_0", "Bees_In_Da_Trap", "Playboytravo"],
        correctAnswer: "0_Cato_0",
    },
    // {
    //     question: "",
    //     choices: ["", "", "", ""],
    //     correctAnswer: "",
    // },
    // {
    //     question: "",
    //     choices: ["", "", "", ""],
    //     correctAnswer: "",
    // },
    // {
    //     question: "",
    //     choices: ["", "", "", ""],
    //     correctAnswer: "",
    // },
]}

export default quiz
